[{
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "And you?",
    "Answer": "¿Y Tú?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Beans",
    "Answer": "Frijoles"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Big/ Small",
    "Answer": "Grande/ Pequeño"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Bless you (when sneezing)",
    "Answer": "¡Salud!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Bless you.",
    "Answer": "Salud."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Call me.",
    "Answer": "Llámame."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Call me. (Talk to me)",
    "Answer": "Háblame."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I enter/come in?",
    "Answer": "Puedo entrar/pasar?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I have a napkin",
    "Answer": " please?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I have more",
    "Answer": " please?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I have one?",
    "Answer": "Puedo tener uno?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I have water",
    "Answer": " please?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can I help you?",
    "Answer": "¿Podría Ayudarse?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can we share?",
    "Answer": "Podemos compartir?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can you help me?",
    "Answer": "¿Puede Ayudarme?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can you help me?",
    "Answer": "Me puedes ayudar?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can you hold this",
    "Answer": " please?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can you loan me $5?",
    "Answer": "Me puedes prestar $5?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can you pass the salt/pepper?",
    "Answer": "Me puede pasar la sal/el pimiento?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can You Say It Again?",
    "Answer": "¡Puede Repetirlo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Can You Speak Slowly?",
    "Answer": "¡Puedes Hablar Más Despacio!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Cheese",
    "Answer": "Queso"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Come with me!",
    "Answer": "¡Venga Conmigo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Common Questions",
    "Answer": "Preguntas Más Frecuentes"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Congratulations!",
    "Answer": "¡felicidades!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Did you like it here?",
    "Answer": "¿Le gusta a usted aquí?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you have change?",
    "Answer": "Tienes cambio?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you have children?",
    "Answer": "Tienes hijos?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you like it?",
    "Answer": "¿Te Gusta? ¿Te Encanta?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you sell _______ here?",
    "Answer": "Se vende ______ aquí?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you speak (English/ Spanish)?",
    "Answer": "¿Hablas (Inglés/ Español)?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you want one?",
    "Answer": "Quieres uno?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Do you want to buy this?",
    "Answer": "¿Quiere comprarlo usted?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Don't worry!",
    "Answer": "¡No Te Preocupes!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Enjoy! (for meals...)",
    "Answer": "¡Que Aproveche!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)",
    "Answer": "¡Perdone! / ¡Oiga!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Excuse me! ( to pass by)",
    "Answer": "¡Perdone! / Disculpe!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Excuse me.",
    "Answer": "Con permiso. OR Perdóname"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Fork",
    "Answer": "Tenedor"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Four",
    "Answer": " Five"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Give me this!",
    "Answer": "¡Dame Eso!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Go straight! then turn left/ right!",
    "Answer": "¡Vaya Ud Derecho! Pues Tuerza Ud por la Izquierda/ Derecha!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good afternoon.",
    "Answer": "Buenas tardes."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good bye!",
    "Answer": "¡Adiós!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good evening!",
    "Answer": "¡Buenas Tardes!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good evening. (greeting)",
    "Answer": "Buenas noches."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good luck!",
    "Answer": "¡Que Tenga Suerte!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good morning!",
    "Answer": "¡Buenos Días!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good morning.",
    "Answer": "Buenos días."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good night and sweet dreams!",
    "Answer": "¡Buenas Noches Y Dulces Sueños!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good night!",
    "Answer": "¡Buenas noches!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good/ Bad/ So-So.",
    "Answer": "Bueno/ Malo/ Así Así"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Good/ So-So.",
    "Answer": "Bíen/ Así Así"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Goodbye.",
    "Answer": "Adiós."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Goodbyes",
    "Answer": "Despedidas"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Greetings",
    "Answer": "Saludos"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hamburger",
    "Answer": "Hamburguesa"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Happy birthday!",
    "Answer": "¡Feliz Cumpleaños!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Happy new year!",
    "Answer": "¡Feliz Año Nuevo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Have a good day!",
    "Answer": "Ten un buen día!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hello",
    "Answer": " my name is John."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hello! How are you?",
    "Answer": "Hola! Cómo estás?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Here you go! (when giving something)",
    "Answer": "¡Aquí Tiene!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hey! Friend!",
    "Answer": "¡Eh! ¡Amigo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hi!",
    "Answer": "¡Hola!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hold on please! (phone)",
    "Answer": "¡No Cuelgue, Por Favor!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How are you?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo está usted?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How are you?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo Estás?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How Do You Say ",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo Se Dice "
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How do you say maybe in Spanish?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo se dice maybe en Español?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How long have you lived here?",
    "Answer": "Cuánto tiempo tienes aquí?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How many are there?",
    "Answer": "¿Cuántos hay?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How much does it cost?",
    "Answer": "¿Cuánto cuesta?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How much does it cost?",
    "Answer": "Cuánto cuesta?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How much is this?",
    "Answer": "¿Cuánto Vale/ Cuesta Eso?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "How old are you?",
    "Answer": "¿Cuántos Años Tienes?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Hurry up!",
    "Answer": "¡Date Prisa!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I am fine.",
    "Answer": "Estoy bien."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I am lost. Where is the restroom?",
    "Answer": "Estoy perdido. ¿Dónde está el baño?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I do not understand.",
    "Answer": "Yo no comprendo."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I Don't Know!",
    "Answer": "¡No (Lo) Sé!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I Don't Understand!",
    "Answer": "¡No Entiendo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I don’t have children.",
    "Answer": "No tengo hijos."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I feel sick.",
    "Answer": "Estoy Mareado"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I have allergies.",
    "Answer": "Tengo alergiás."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I Have No Idea.",
    "Answer": "¡No Tengo Ni Idea!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I have to go",
    "Answer": "Me Tengo Que Ir."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I have two sons/daughters.",
    "Answer": "Tengo dos hijos/hijas."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I hope you have a good day!",
    "Answer": "Que tenga un buen día!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I like Spanish",
    "Answer": "Me Gusta El Español"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I live in (the U.S/ Spain)",
    "Answer": "Vivo En (los Estados Unidos/ España)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I love you!",
    "Answer": "¡Te Quiero!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I missed you so much!",
    "Answer": "Te extrañé mucho!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I need a doctor",
    "Answer": "!Necesito un medico!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I need to practice my Spanish",
    "Answer": "me falta práctica en Español"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I really like it!",
    "Answer": "¡Me Gusta/ Encanta Mucho!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I want a…",
    "Answer": "Quiero un…"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I will be right back!",
    "Answer": "Regreso En Un Momentito."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I work as a (translator/ businessman)",
    "Answer": "Trabajo Como (Traductor/ Hombre de Negocios)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I would like…",
    "Answer": "Me gustaría…"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'd like to visit Spain one day",
    "Answer": "Me Gustaría Visitar Algún Día Tu País"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm (American)",
    "Answer": "Soy (americano/ americana)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm (twenty",
    "Answer": " thirty...) years old."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm fine",
    "Answer": " thanks!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm from (the U.S/ Spain)",
    "Answer": "Soy De (los Estados Unidos/ España..) / Soy (americano)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm hungry/ thirsty.",
    "Answer": "Tengo Hambre/ Sed."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm looking for john.",
    "Answer": "Estoy Buscando A Juan."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm lost",
    "Answer": "Estoy perdido"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm Sorry! (if you don't hear something)",
    "Answer": "¡Discuple!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I'm sorry.",
    "Answer": "Lo siento."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I've been learning Spanish for 1 month",
    "Answer": "Tengo Un Mes Estudiando Español"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I’m a doctor",
    "Answer": " professor"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I’m a vegetarian/vegan.",
    "Answer": "Soy vegetariano/vegan."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "I’m from ____________.",
    "Answer": "Soy de _____________."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "In The Morning/ Evening/ At Night.",
    "Answer": "Por La Mañana/ Tarde/ Noche."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "It was a pleasure to meet you.",
    "Answer": "Fue un placer conocerte."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "It's 10 o'clock. 07:30pm.",
    "Answer": "Son las diez en punto. Las siete y media."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Just a little.",
    "Answer": "Solo Un Poquito."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Knife",
    "Answer": "Cuchillo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Lettuce",
    "Answer": "Lechuga"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Lime/lemon",
    "Answer": "Limón"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Look!",
    "Answer": "¡Mira!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Me/ You. Him/ Her.",
    "Answer": "Yo/ Tú. Él/ Ella"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Merry Christmas!",
    "Answer": "¡Feliz Navidad!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Mr.../ Mrs.…/ Miss…",
    "Answer": "Señor.../ Señora.../ Señorita..."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "My name is __________.",
    "Answer": "Me llamo __________."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "My name is ...",
    "Answer": "Me llamo ..."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "My Spanish is bad.",
    "Answer": "Mi Español Es Malo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Nice to meet you!",
    "Answer": "¡Tanto Gusto! / Medio Gusto Conocerte!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Nice to meet you.",
    "Answer": "Mucho gusto."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "No meat",
    "Answer": " please."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "No Problem!",
    "Answer": "¡No Problema!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "No.",
    "Answer": "No."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Nothing much",
    "Answer": "Nada"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Oh! That's good!",
    "Answer": "!Oh, qué bueno!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "One beer",
    "Answer": " please."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "One glass of red/white wine",
    "Answer": " please."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "One moment please!",
    "Answer": "¡Un Momento, Por Favor!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "One",
    "Answer": " Two"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Pasta",
    "Answer": "Pasta"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Please.",
    "Answer": "Por favor."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Really!",
    "Answer": "¡Verdad!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Rice",
    "Answer": "Arróz"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Sandwich",
    "Answer": "Sándwich, Bocadillo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Say hi to John for me",
    "Answer": "Dale Saludos A ( Juan ...) De Mi Parte"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "See you in a little bit!",
    "Answer": "Nos vemos al rato! (en México)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "See you later!",
    "Answer": "¡Hasta luego!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "See you later!",
    "Answer": "Hasta luego!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "See you later.",
    "Answer": "Hasta luego."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Seven",
    "Answer": " Eight"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Sorry (for a mistake)",
    "Answer": "¡Lo Siento!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Spain is a wonderful country",
    "Answer": "España Es Un País Maravelloso"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Spoon",
    "Answer": "Cuchara"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Straw",
    "Answer": "Popote"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Thank you (very much)!",
    "Answer": "¡(Muchas) Gracias!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Thank you.",
    "Answer": "Gracías."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "There are many.",
    "Answer": "Hay muchos."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "This/ That. Here/There",
    "Answer": "Eso/Ese. Aquí/ Allí"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Today/ Now",
    "Answer": "Hoy/ Ahora"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Tomato",
    "Answer": "Tomate"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Tomorrow/ Yesterday",
    "Answer": "Mañana/ Ayer"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "We’ll meet on _________ (day).",
    "Answer": "Nos reunimos el ________ (día)."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "We’ll see each other later!",
    "Answer": "Nos vemos!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "We’ll talk later.",
    "Answer": "Nos hablamos luego."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Welcome! (to greet someone)",
    "Answer": "¡Bienvenido!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What do you do for a living?",
    "Answer": "¿A Qué Te Dedicas?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What Does ",
    "Answer": "¿Qué Quiere Decir "
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What Is This?",
    "Answer": "¿Qué Es Esto?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What is your last name?",
    "Answer": "Cuál es tu apellido?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What is your name?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo se llama usted?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What time is it?",
    "Answer": "¿Qué hora es?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What would you like to drink?",
    "Answer": "Qué le gustaría tomar/beber?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What would you like to eat?",
    "Answer": "Qué le gustaría comer?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What? Where?",
    "Answer": "¿Qué? ¿Dónde?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What's new?",
    "Answer": "¿Qué Hay De Nuevo?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What's That Called In Spanish?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo Se llama a Esto En Español?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What's your name?",
    "Answer": "¿Cómo te llamas?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "What’s your name?",
    "Answer": "Cómo te llamas?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where are we right now?",
    "Answer": "Dónde estamos ahora?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where are you from?",
    "Answer": "¿De Dónde Eres?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where are you from?",
    "Answer": "De dónde eres?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where do you live?",
    "Answer": "¿Dónde Vives?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where do you live?",
    "Answer": "Dónde vives?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where do you work?",
    "Answer": "Dónde trabajas?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where is my room?",
    "Answer": "Dónde está mi cuarto?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where is the __________ street?",
    "Answer": "Dónde está la calle ________?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where is the (bathroom/ pharmacy)?",
    "Answer": "¿Dónde Está (el Baño/ la Farmacia)?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where is the bathroom?",
    "Answer": "Dónde está el baño?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Where is the bus?",
    "Answer": "Dónde está el autobús?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Who?",
    "Answer": "¿Quièn?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Why?",
    "Answer": "¿Por què?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "With…",
    "Answer": "Con…"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Without…",
    "Answer": "Sin…"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Would you speak slower",
    "Answer": " please."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Write It Down Please!",
    "Answer": "¡Escríbalo, Por Favor!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Yes.",
    "Answer": "Sí."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "Yes/ No",
    "Answer": "Sí/ No"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "You are welcome (it was nothing).",
    "Answer": "De nada."
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "You're very kind!",
    "Answer": "¡Eres Muy Amable!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Spanish",
    "Question": "You're welcome! (for ",
    "Answer": "¡De Nada!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "See you later!",
    "Answer": "A dopo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...fizzy water",
    "Answer": "acqua gassata"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...still water",
    "Answer": "acqua non gassata"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Goodbye",
    "Answer": "Arrivederci"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good bye!",
    "Answer": "Arrivederci!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Hold on please! (phone)",
    "Answer": "Attenda prego!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good, thank you",
    "Answer": "Bene, grazie"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm fine, thanks!",
    "Answer": "Bene, grazie!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good/ So-So.",
    "Answer": "Bene/ così e così."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Welcome! (to greet someone)",
    "Answer": "Benvenuto!/ Benvenuta! (female)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...beer",
    "Answer": "birra"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "steak",
    "Answer": "bistecca"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Enjoy! (for meals...)",
    "Answer": "Buon appetito!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Happy birthday!",
    "Answer": "Buon compleanno!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good day",
    "Answer": "Buon giorno"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Merry Christmas!",
    "Answer": "Buon natale!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good luck!",
    "Answer": "Buona fortuna!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good night",
    "Answer": "Buona notte"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good night and sweet dreams!",
    "Answer": "Buona notte e sogni d'oro!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good night!",
    "Answer": "Buona notte!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good evening",
    "Answer": "Buona sera"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good evening!",
    "Answer": "Buona sera!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good morning!",
    "Answer": "Buongiorno!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Good/ Bad/ So-So.",
    "Answer": "Buono/ Cattivo/ Così e così"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Is there a cheaper one?",
    "Answer": "C'é una più economica?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Is there WiFi?",
    "Answer": "C'é WiFi?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I understand.",
    "Answer": "Capisco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "meat",
    "Answer": "carne"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What time is it?",
    "Answer": "Che ore sono?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Hi!",
    "Answer": "Ciao!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Hey! Friend!",
    "Answer": "Ciao! Amico!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How Do You Say ",
    "Answer": "Come dite “please” in italiano?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What's That Called In Italian?",
    "Answer": "Come si chiama quella cosa in italiano?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How are you?",
    "Answer": "Come stai?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How are you?",
    "Answer": "Come stai?/ Come state (polite)?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What’s your name?",
    "Answer": "Come ti chiami?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "with private bathroom",
    "Answer": "con bagno"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Congratulations!",
    "Answer": "Congratulazioni!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What Is This?",
    "Answer": "Cos'è questa cosa?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What's new?",
    "Answer": "Cosa c'è di nuovo?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What do you do for a living?",
    "Answer": "cosa fai per vivere?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What Does ",
    "Answer": "Cosa significa "
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What does that mean?",
    "Answer": "Cosa significa?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What are you doing (at the moment)?",
    "Answer": "Cosa stai facendo adesso?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What do you like doing?",
    "Answer": "Cosa ti piace fare?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What? Where?",
    "Answer": "Cosa? Dove?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "side dish [veggies always come seperately]",
    "Answer": "cotorno"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Give me this!",
    "Answer": "Dammi questo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Really!",
    "Answer": "Davvero!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I have to go",
    "Answer": "Devo andare"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Where are you from?",
    "Answer": "Di dove sei?/ Di dove è? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "In The Morning/ Evening/ At Night.",
    "Answer": "Di mattina/ Di sera/ Di notte. "
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "dessert",
    "Answer": "dolce"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Tomorrow/ Yesterday",
    "Answer": "Domani/ ieri"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "double room for single use [will often be offered if singles are unavailable]",
    "Answer": "doppia uso singola"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Where is?",
    "Answer": "Dov'é"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Where do you live?",
    "Answer": "Dove abiti?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Where is the (bathroom/ pharmacy)?",
    "Answer": "Dove posso trovare (il bagno/ la farmacia?)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Where do you live?",
    "Answer": "Dove vivi?/ Dove vive? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "and",
    "Answer": "e"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Is service included?",
    "Answer": "É incluso il servizio?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Is breakfast included?",
    "Answer": "É incluso la prima colazione?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "That's too much",
    "Answer": "É troppo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "And you?",
    "Answer": "e tu? e lei? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Nice to meet you!",
    "Answer": "è un piacere conoscerti!/ è un piacere conoscerla (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Here you go! (when giving something)",
    "Answer": "Eccolo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Happy new year!",
    "Answer": "Felice anno nuovo!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Oh! That's good!",
    "Answer": "Grande!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Big/ Small",
    "Answer": "Grande/ Piccolo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "thanks",
    "Answer": "grazie"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "thank you",
    "Answer": "grazie"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "thank you very much",
    "Answer": "grazie mille"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Thank you (very much)!",
    "Answer": "Grazie! / (Molte grazie)!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Look!",
    "Answer": "Guarda!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I’m [...] years old.",
    "Answer": "Ho … anni"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm (twenty, thirty...) years old.",
    "Answer": "Ho (venti, trenta …) anni."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I need to practice my Italian",
    "Answer": "ho bisogno di fare pratica con il mio italiano"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I need a doctor",
    "Answer": "Ho bisogno di un dottore!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Check, please",
    "Answer": "Il conto, per favore"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "My Italian is bad.",
    "Answer": "il mio italiano è orribile."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "My first name is [...]",
    "Answer": "Il mio nome è"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Me/ You. Him/ Her.",
    "Answer": "io/ tu, voi (you polite). Lui/ Lei"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "English Greetings",
    "Answer": "Italian Greetings:"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Italy is a wonderful country",
    "Answer": "L'italia è un paese meraviglioso."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I work as a (translator/ businessman)",
    "Answer": "Lavoro come (traduttore/ uomo d'affari)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Do you speak english? (formal)",
    "Answer": "Lei parla Inglese?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a half-liter of",
    "Answer": "mezzo litro di"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "My name is [...].",
    "Answer": "mi chiamo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "My name is ...",
    "Answer": "Mi chiamo ..."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm sorry",
    "Answer": "Mi dispiace"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I really like it!",
    "Answer": "Mi piace davvero."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I like Italian",
    "Answer": "Mi piace l'italiano."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'd like to visit Italy one day",
    "Answer": "Mi piacerebbe visitare l'Italia un giorno di questi!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Excuse me!",
    "Answer": "Mi scusi!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm Sorry! (if you don't hear something)",
    "Answer": "Mi scusi? / Prego ?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I missed you so much!",
    "Answer": "Mi sei mancato molto!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I feel sick.",
    "Answer": "Mi sento male!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm lost",
    "Answer": "Mi sono perso/ persa (feminine)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "very bad",
    "Answer": "molto male"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "no",
    "Answer": "no"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "No, I don’t speak english.",
    "Answer": "No, non parlo inglese"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "No Problem!",
    "Answer": "Non c'è problema!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I don’t understand",
    "Answer": "Non capisco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I don't understand",
    "Answer": "Non capisco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I Don't Understand!",
    "Answer": "Non capisco!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I don’t know.",
    "Answer": "non lo so"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I Don't Know!",
    "Answer": "Non lo so!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Not bad, thanks!",
    "Answer": "Non male, grazie!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Nothing much",
    "Answer": "Non molto"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I Have No Idea.",
    "Answer": "Non ne ho idea!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I don’t speak Polish.",
    "Answer": "Non parlo Polacco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Don't worry!",
    "Answer": "non ti preoccupare !"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Today/ Now",
    "Answer": "Oggi/ Adesso"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Do you speak English?",
    "Answer": "Parla Inglese?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Please talk more slowly!",
    "Answer": "Parla più piano perfavore!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Do you speak (English/ Italian)?",
    "Answer": "Parli (inglese/italiano)?/ Parla (inglese/italiano)? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Do you speak english? (informal)",
    "Answer": "Parli Inglese?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I speak a little Polish.",
    "Answer": "Parlo poco Polacco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "for two nights",
    "Answer": "per due notti"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "please",
    "Answer": "per favore"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...for 8pm",
    "Answer": "per le otto"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...for 7pm",
    "Answer": "per le sette"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...for 7:30pm",
    "Answer": "per le sette e mezzo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "please / you’re welcome",
    "Answer": "Per piacere / prego or figurati"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "for three nights",
    "Answer": "per tre notti"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "for one night",
    "Answer": "per una notte"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Excuse me! ( to pass by)",
    "Answer": "Permesso"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "fish",
    "Answer": "pesce"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Nice to meet you!",
    "Answer": "Piacere di conoscerti!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "chicken",
    "Answer": "pollo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Can I help you?",
    "Answer": "Posso aiutarti?/ posso aiutarla (polite)?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "May I see the room?",
    "Answer": "Posso vedere la camera?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Can you help me?",
    "Answer": "Potresti aiutarmi?/ potrebbe aiutarmi? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Can You Say It Again?",
    "Answer": "Potresti ripetere per favore?/ Potrebbe ripetere per favore? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "You're welcome! (for ",
    "Answer": "Prego!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Hello (on the phone) / I beg your pardon?",
    "Answer": "Pronto"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Can You Speak Slowly?",
    "Answer": "Puoi parlare lentamente? Potrebbe parlare lentamente? (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What’s your first name?",
    "Answer": "Qual'e il tuo nome?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What's your name?",
    "Answer": "Quale è il suo nome?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "What are your hobbies?",
    "Answer": "Quali sono i tuoi hobby?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How old are you?",
    "Answer": "Quanti anni hai?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How much is this?",
    "Answer": "Quanto costa questo?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "How much is...?",
    "Answer": "Quanto costa?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Four, Five, Six",
    "Answer": "Quattro, Cinque, Sei."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...that",
    "Answer": "quello"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...this",
    "Answer": "questo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "This/ That. Here/There",
    "Answer": "Questo/ Quello. Qui/ Li."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Say hi to John for me",
    "Answer": "Saluta John da parte mia!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Bless you (when sneezing)",
    "Answer": "Salute!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Hurry up!",
    "Answer": "Sbrigati!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Write It Down Please!",
    "Answer": "Scrivilo per favore!/ Lo scriva per favore (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Sorry (for a mistake)",
    "Answer": "Scusami!/ Mi scusi! (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Excuse me ...! (to ask for something)",
    "Answer": "Scusami!/ Mi scusi! (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Excuse me (to get attention)",
    "Answer": "Scusi"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "You're very kind!",
    "Answer": "Sei molto gentile!/ lei è molto gentile (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "you’re very welcome",
    "Answer": "Sei veramente il benvenuto"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "without private bathroom",
    "Answer": "senza bagno [they might say con bagno in comune—"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Seven, Eight, Nine, Ten",
    "Answer": "Sette, Otto, Nove, Dieci."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "yes",
    "Answer": "si"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Yes, I do speak english.",
    "Answer": "Si, parlo inglese."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Yes/ No",
    "Answer": "Si/ No"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Mr.../ Mrs.…/ Miss…",
    "Answer": "Signor …/ Signora …/ Signorina"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Just a little.",
    "Answer": "Solo un po'."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm from (the U.S/ Italy)",
    "Answer": "Sono (statunitense, italiano)."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm hungry/ thirsty.",
    "Answer": "Sono Affamato/ Assetato."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm (American)",
    "Answer": "Sono americano."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "It's 10 o'clock. 07:30pm.",
    "Answer": "Sono le dieci in punto. Le sette e trenta"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I am vegetarian",
    "Answer": "sono vegetariano"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I’m well, thanks!",
    "Answer": "Sto bene, grazie!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I'm looking for john.",
    "Answer": "Sto cercando John."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I've been learning Italian for 1 month",
    "Answer": "Sto imparando l'italiano da un mese."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I love you!",
    "Answer": "Ti amo!/ Ti voglio bene!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Did you like it here?",
    "Answer": "ti piace qui?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Do you like it?",
    "Answer": "Ti piace?"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I will be right back!",
    "Answer": "Torno subito!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a farm stay",
    "Answer": "un agriturismo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a hotel",
    "Answer": "un albergo"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...an apartment for rent",
    "Answer": "un appartamento"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a B&B",
    "Answer": "un bed-and-breakfast"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a glass of",
    "Answer": "un bicchiere di"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "One moment please!",
    "Answer": "Un momento prego!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a hostel",
    "Answer": "un ostello"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...some (of)",
    "Answer": "un pó (di)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a restaurant",
    "Answer": "un ristorante"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a rental room",
    "Answer": "un'affittacamera"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a bottle of",
    "Answer": "una bottiglia di"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "a double room with two beds",
    "Answer": "una doppia con due letti"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "a double room with one big bed",
    "Answer": "una matrimoniale"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "a single room",
    "Answer": "una singola"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "a table for two",
    "Answer": "una tavola per due"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...a casual restaurant",
    "Answer": "una trattoria"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "triple room",
    "Answer": "una tripla"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "One, Two, Three",
    "Answer": "Uno, Due, Tre."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Go straight! then turn left/ right!",
    "Answer": "Vada dritto! e poi giri a destra/ sinistra!"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "Come with me!",
    "Answer": "Vieni con me!/ Venga con me! (polite)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...white wine",
    "Answer": "vino bianco"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "...red wine",
    "Answer": "vino rosso"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "veal",
    "Answer": "vitello"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I live in (the U.S/ Italy)",
    "Answer": "Vivo (negli stati uniti / in Italia)"
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I would like to reserve...",
    "Answer": "Vorrei prenotare..."
}, {
    "Subject": "Italian",
    "Question": "I would like",
    "Answer": "Vorrei..."
}]